<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Somaiya Classroom</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign In/Sign Up</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."</string>
    <string name="forpass"><u>Forgot Password?</u></string>
    <string name="SYL">SYlLABUS</string>
    <string name="TEXT">Welcome To Student Portal</string>
    <string name="COURSE">COURSE MATERIAL</string>
    <string name="CALENDAR">CALENDAR</string>
    <string name="EASYSOL">EASY SOLUTION</string>
    <string name="TEXT2">PLEASE PAY TO ACCESS</string>
    <string name="TEXT3">CLICK HERE TO DOWNLOAD SYLLABUS</string>
    <string name="TEXT4">CONTENTS</string>
    <string name="DWNLD">DOWNLOAD</string>
    <string name="pay1">NET BANKING</string>
    <string name="pay2">CARD PAYMENT</string>
    <string name="termtest">TERM TEST PAPERS</string>
    <string name="ese">END SEM PAPERS</string>
    <string name="PRESS">PRESS TO DOWNLOAD</string>
    <string name="dwnld2">SELECT TO DOWNLOAD</string>
    <string name="PPT">PowerPoints</string>
    <string name="Pracs">Practicals</string>
    <string name="Quiz">Quiz</string>
    <string name="Tuts">Tutorials</string>
    <string name="lst">LAST YR PAPERS</string>
    <string name="Open">OPEN</string>
    <string name="Close">CLOSE</string>
    <!--Shared Preference keys-->
    <string name="USER_INFO">com.example.somaiya.somaiyaclassroom.PREF_USER_INFO</string>
    <string name="pref_key_name">name</string>
    <string name="pref_key_svv_mail">svv_mail</string>
    <string name="pref_key_email">email</string>
    <string name="pref_key_pic_url">picUrl</string>
    <string name="display_name">Username</string>
    <string-array name="list">
        <item name="chap1">Chapter 1.  Introduction to C</item>

        <item>Chapter 2.  Basic Operators</item>

        <item>Chapter 3.  Control Structures</item>

        <item>Chapter 4.  Arrays and Structures</item>

        <item>Chapter 5.  User Defined Functions</item>

        <item>Chapter 6.  Pointers and Files</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="names">

        <item>Select Bank</item>
        <item>Axis Bank</item>
        <item>Bank Of Baroda</item>
        <item>Bank of Maharashtra</item>
        <item>Bank Of India</item>
        <item>Canara Bank</item>
        <item>Dena Bank</item>
        <item>HDFC Bank</item>
        <item>ICICI Bank</item>
        <item>State Bank of India</item>

        <item>Yes Bank</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="faq_stu">

        <item><b>What are easy solutions and why do I need to pay for the same?</b>\n\nEasy Solutions are the comprehensive solutions for the past years’ question papers of KJSCE; prepared cohesively by the respective subject faculty. These solutions are “marking-scheme specific” and give an excellent idea about the answer expectations with respect to length of the answers and content of the answers. The weightage of this valuable resource makes it a paid one.\n</item>

        <item><b>\nIs PayPal a secure site for my online transactions?</b>\n\nPaypal is the easiest way to make payments online. While checking out your order, you will be redirected to the Paypal website. Be sure to fill in correct details for fast  hassle-free payment processing. After a successful Paypal payment, a payment advice will be automatically generated to Samplestore.com system for your order. It's fast, easy and secure.\n</item>

        <item><b>\nHow do I cancel my order, under considerate circumstances, after the amount is already paid?</b>\n\nYou may have to confront the A/O for the refund, which will strictly be subjected to extreme cases.\n</item>

        <item><b>\nAre we allowed offline mode of payment for easy solutions, for necessary reasons if any? </b>\n\nNo.The students should strictly use the online options such as net banking and PayPal that are being provided in the App.\n</item>

       <item><b>\nI click on a card to download but nothing happens. Why is it so?</b>\n\n1.Go to app settings of your phone and then go to Google Drive.\n2.Set Open Link to \"Always Ask\" and then retry downloading.\nIf it still does not download, write to us at the e-mail address below.\nIt is recommended that you choose Google Chrome to download different file formats (PDFs, JPEGs,DOCX, PPTX, XLSX).\n </item>

        <item><b>\nHow do I contact the professor for queries?</b>\n\nThe navigation view has a “Ask a doubt” tab, which will direct you to your default mailing app. You can then mail your concerns to your professor.\n</item>

        <item><b>\nHow do I notify developers about force crash, if any?</b>\n\nDo not worry. We have set up Crashlytics, which sends us real time force crash issues, so that user does not have to take the initiative of finding logcats and then mailing it to us separately.\n</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="faq_tch">

        <item><b>\nHow do I upload the new updated syllabus?</b>\n\nThe new syllabus uploaded by you will automatically overwrite the old one. Hence no issues.\n</item>

        <item><b>\nDo I get to change the name of the file uploaded?</b>\n\nNo. You have to name the file properly and then upload. Please set an appropriate name before uploading for convenience of the students to understand what is in the file.\n</item>

        <item><b>\nShould the previous year papers be categorised before uploading?</b>\n\nYes. You should upload them separately under the “Term test papers” and “End Sem Papers\" Section.\n</item>

        <item><b>\nHow does Add Events enhance the flexibility of our interaction with students?</b>\n\nYou can easily add events for tests, viva, practical schedule, quiz, lecture cancellation etc. and the students will be notified about the same.\n</item>

        <item><b>\nHow do I notify developers about force crash, if any?</b>\n\nDo not worry. We have set up Crashlytics, which sends us real time force crash issues and sends us the relevant logs to work upon, so that user doesn\'t have to take the initiative of finding logcats and then mailing it to us separately.\n</item>

    </string-array>


    <string name="faq"><u>developer.somaiyaclassroom@gmail.com</u></string>


</resources>